<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. [CHAR LIMIT=12] -->
    <string name="app_name">San Diego</string>

    <!-- Category name for phrases [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_beaches">Beaches</string>

    <string name="beach_1">Ka\'anapali Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_1_description">Once a retreat for Hawaiian royalty and today is often called one of the best beaches on Maui.</string>
    <string name="beach_2">Keawakapu Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_2_description">This secret south Maui paradise is an ideal getaway for white sand beach and an underwater reef.</string>
    <string name="beach_3">Kapalua Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_3_description">The calm waters offer great swimming, and natural tide pools give children the opportunity to see sea creatures up close.</string>
    <string name="beach_4">Kahekili Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_4_description">This extension of Kaʻanapali Beach is an ideal spot for snorkeling and scuba diving.</string>
    <string name="beach_5">Napili Bay</string>
    <string name="beach_5_description">Napili Bay is well known for its golden sand, great snorkeling and picture-perfect sunsets.</string>
    <string name="beach_6">Baby Beach</string>
    <string name="beach_6_description">Beautiful, calm waters make for great snorkeling and swimming for the kids.</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary words for colors [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_entertainment">Activities</string>
    <string name="activities_1">SeaWorld</string>
    <string name="activities_1_description">Spread across the beautiful Mission Bay Park, SeaWorld is known for its amazing animals, interactive attractions and rides.</string>
    <string name="activities_2">San Diego Zoo</string>
    <string name="activities_2_description">San Diego zoo is a tropical oasis with amazing habitats for gorillas, Komodo dragons, tigers, polar bears, and pandas.</string>
    <string name="activities_3">LegoLand</string>
    <string name="activities_3_description">Families can enjoy rides, shows and attractions! Marvel at cities built entirely out of millions of LEGO® bricks.</string>
    <string name="activities_4">Maritime Museum</string>
    <string name="activities_4_description">Experience a world-class collection of historic sailing ships, steam-powered boats, and submarines.</string>
    <string name="activities_5">Cabrillo National Park</string>
    <string name="activities_5_description">San Diego's 'only' National Park offers tremendous views and excellent opportunities to explore it's history.</string>
    <string name="activities_6">Belmont Park Amusement</string>
    <string name="activities_6_description">Located on Mission Beach, Belmont Park is San Diego's only beachfront amusement and entertainment center!</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary words for numbers [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_restaurants">Dining</string>
    <string name="restaurant_1">Coasterra</string>
    <string name="restaurant_1_description">Boasting stunning views of the San Diego Harbor, Coasterra is the ideal destination for intimate sunset dining.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2">Peohe\'s</string>
    <string name="restaurant_2_description">Peohe’s captures the essence of Southern California dining with its stunning bay front views and a chic tropical vibe.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3">Blue Point Coastal Cuisine</string>
    <string name="restaurant_3_description">Blue Point was the first seafood and oyster bar to open in the Gaslamp and it remains one of the very best.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4">George\'s At the Cove</string>
    <string name="restaurant_4_description">This three-floor oceanview stunner offers choose-your-own-adventure dining, spanning a casual rooftop terrace.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5">Starlite</string>
    <string name="restaurant_5_description">Starlite helped kickstart the concept of a craft cocktail bar that serves great food and is still one of the best.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6">Civico 1845</string>
    <string name="restaurant_6_description">This restaurant offers menu of Southern Italian seafood dishes made with modern innovations on Italian classics.</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary words for family members [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_shopping">Shopping</string>
    <string name="shopping_1">Lanefield</string>
    <string name="shopping_1_description">Lane Field Park Markets is a beautiful open air food market serving craft coffee and food from local vendors.</string>
    <string name="shopping_2">Del Mar Highlands Town Center</string>
    <string name="shopping_2_description">Shop, dine, relax and explore Del Mar Highlands Town Center located in the heart of Carmel Valley.</string>
    <string name="shopping_3">Westfield UTC</string>
    <string name="shopping_3_description">Westfield UTC is San Diego's iconic, open-air shopping, dining and entertainment destination.</string>
    <string name="shopping_4">Las Americas Premium Outlets</string>
    <string name="shopping_4_description">Stroll through the center's beautiful courtyards with fountains, statues and elegant architecture.</string>
    <string name="shopping_5">Bazaar Del Mundo</string>
    <string name="shopping_5_description">The Bazaar del Mundo Shops is a great spot for handcrafted gifts and treasures that are unique in all the world.</string>
    <string name="shopping_6">Shops at the Del</string>
    <string name="shopping_6_description">Explore Shops at The Del, a colorful bazaar of designer labels, fine jewelry, home accents, bath and spa products.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
